你可以选择左侧列表上的设备，
Here you can see hierarchy view lets you select from
从物理和虚拟上看到层次结构视图，
a list of devices with physical and virtual on the left,
每一个都包含其运行活动，
each of which then contains each of the running activities
可以在设备列表中选择。
and applications running on that device. You simply select the activity
你只需要选择你想分析的应用程序的activity。
from the application that you want to profile. Then, hit
然后，点击这里的Load View hierarchy按钮，
the Load View hierarchy button here, and you'll see a representation
你将会看见所选的activity的视图层次，以树状图形式从左至右表现在这里。
of the selected activity's entire view hierarchy represented here in the
你可以看到，
Tree View, from left to right. You can see that the
整个层次结构在这里展示，在线框架中程序的概览和布局本身也会显示出来。
entire hierarchy is also shown here, in the overview and the layout
点击层次结构中的任何视图，
itself is shown in a wire frame here. Clicking on any view,
将会展示我们所点的视图的具体显示内容，
at any point within the hierarchy, will show you what is displayed,
并展示在这个层次结构中，指向下一个视图的数量。
showing us the number of views which are contained within the hierarchy
你也可以获取performance metrics，
from this point onwards. You can also obtain the performance metrics to
用来测试布局和绘制层次结构中的每一个元素需要多长时间。
find out how long it takes to measure, layout and draw each
这是一个强大的工具，
element of the hierarchy. It's a powerful tool and you can find
你可以从下方的链接找到视频与使用指南进行学习，
out more about how to use it to optimize your layouts and
来优化你的布局与视图。
views in the videos and guides linked to from the
现在，我们将用这个工具来找到，
instructor notes below. For now, note that we can use
一个需要被展平的深度嵌套布局。
it to find surprisingly deeply nested layouts that need to
举个例子，这有一个布局，
be flattened. For example, here we have a layout we
我们可以使用以下两种方法中的一种。
can describe using one of two techniques. One solution is
一种解决方案是使用两个嵌套线性布局。
using two nested linear layouts. But a better solution would
但更好的办法是使用相对布局。相对布局的层次会更浅一点。
be using a relative layout. The relative layout is one
另一种技巧是避免在根布局下使用框架布局，
level shallower. Another tip is to avoid using the frame layout
可以将视图以子视图的方式插入其中。
as the root for layout that will always be inserted
在这种情况下，合并标签是一个更好的选择。
as a child into another one. In these circumstances, the merge
当布局被放在parents hierarchy中，标签将被消除。
tag is a better alternative. This will be eliminated when the
为了帮助你记住所有的技巧和提示，
layout is included into the parents hierarchy. To help you remember
Android提供了一个强大的静态分析工具，称为Lint。
all of these tips and tips, Android has a powerful static
你可以在这里看见Lint的窗口，
analysis tool called Lint. As you can see here in the
除了我们已经说过的布局警告问题，
lint window, in addition to the layout warnings we've already talked
这里也可以检查问题，
about, it also checks from
包括可访问性、翻译是否完整、硬编码字符串等问题。
everything from accessibility problems, missing translations,
在提供的笔记链接中，
and hard coded strings. You can find all the things lint checks
你可以找到Lint检查的开发者工具页面信息。
for at the developer tools page linked to in the instructor notes